Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition UP039
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition
2005 -- 2013
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
UP039
0.5 Linear Feet
14 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection is organized in one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition which started in September 2005. It was created as an e-newsletter to improve communication within the Friedman School community. A new issues comes out every six weeks during the academic year. DCA holds paper print-outs of the newsletter from September 2005 through July 2007. Subsequent issues are available as PDFs.
Biographical / Historical
The Tufts School of Nutrition Science and Policy was established in 1981 and renamed the Gerald J. and Dorothy R. Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy in 2001. Its mission is to improve the nutritional health and well-being of populations throughout the world.
- Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2005 -- 2013; UP039.001; 0.5 Linear Feet; 14 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series is comprised of Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, an e-newsletter from the Dean of the Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2005-09; UP039.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2005-11; UP039.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2005-12; UP039.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2006-02; UP039.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2006-03; UP039.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2006-05; UP039.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2006-09; UP039.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2006-11; UP039.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2006-12; UP039.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2007-01; UP039.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2007-03; UP039.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2007-05; UP039.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2007-07; UP039.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2007-09; UP039.001.002.00001; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
    No volume or issue information.
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2007-11; UP039.001.002.00002; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2007-12; UP039.001.002.00003; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2008-01; UP039.001.002.00004; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2008-03; UP039.001.002.00005; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2008-05; UP039.001.002.00006; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2008-06; UP039.001.002.00007; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2008-09; UP039.001.002.00008; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2008-11; UP039.001.002.00009; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2008-12; UP039.001.002.00010; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2009-01; UP039.001.002.00011; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2009-03; UP039.001.002.00012; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2009-04; UP039.001.002.00013; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2009-06; UP039.001.002.00014; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2009-09; UP039.001.002.00015; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2009-11; UP039.001.002.00016; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2009-12; UP039.001.002.00017; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2010-01; UP039.001.002.00018; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2010-03; UP039.001.002.00019; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2010-04; UP039.001.002.00020; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2010-06; UP039.001.002.00021; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2010-09; UP039.001.002.00022; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2010-11; UP039.001.002.00023; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2010-12; UP039.001.002.00024; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2011-01; UP039.001.002.00025; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2011-06; UP039.001.002.00026; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
  - Dean's Letter for Tufts Nutrition, 2013-10; UP039.001.002.00027; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy